ANDRE STÁBILE

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

SOCIAL

arquiduqueandre@gmail.com



andrestabile.com

PROFILE

Highly qualified, researcher, autodidact and experienced in short term projects, individually and in groups. Have varied knowledge in information system, administration and human learning. In love with product creation and inspired by innovative environments. Fluent in Portuguese and English, advanced Spanish.

EXPERTISE

User Experience Design User Interface Design Adobe Creative Suite HTML **CSS lavascript** Team Leadership Project Management

SKILLS

Leadership Communication Research Technical Writing Strategic Planning

EXPERIENCE

2018 - Present

AML Consulting | UX/UI Developer

- Manage, analyze and rebuild 8 different systems between ERPs and CRMs simultaneously.
- Apply new concepts of user experience into moneylaundering prevention legacy systems.

2017 - Present

VILAGE Intellectual Property | Product Designer

- Analyze and redesign the company's ERP used by more than 100 employees.
- Plan, design and develop a CRM for more than 35,000 clients, giving them full access to the company's processes.
- Manage and guide a team of developers into building the company's projects.

2012 - 2017

Freelancer | User Experience Designer

- · Execute interactive and visual design as part of a multidisciplinary teams.
- Research and development in interactive design, visual design, UX and new technologies.

EDUCATION

Specialization in User Interface Design 2018 - 2019

University of Minnesota

2016 User Experience Design School

Springboard

Bachelor of Computer Science 2012 - 2015

São Paulo State University - UNESP

VOLUNTEERING

2017 | AIESEC

Vice-President of People Management

- Plan, organize and realize recruitment, induction and education plan for AIESEC members.
- · Control Human Resources Data: member retention, development and productivity.

2017 - Present | Cantinho Afetivo Co-founder and Vice-president

• Plan, organize and/or realize public spaces revitalizations, capoeira, graffiti, cooking and guitar lessons, aesthetics treatments and other courses.